3dsemulator.org 2017-12-12

# Privacy Policy - 3dsemulator.org

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you click on ads. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or N/A. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..

 **Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://3dsemulator.org/privacy-policy.html>

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

 **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

http://3dsemulator.org/contact.html  
[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  
This policy is powered by Trust Guard PCI compliance scans.
